The disaster relief journey is long and perilous.
I hope Teacher returns safely.
When that time comes,
I will host a welcome banquet for Teacher.
Don't worry.
Chancellor Shen will be fine.
Your Majesty.
Because Chancellor Shen insisted on leading the relief efforts personally,
he was secretly poisoned and is in critical condition.
I know. You may leave.
This is the chess set Teacher gave me.
I can't lose it. I can't lose it.
The game is set.
A move made cannot be taken back.
The only thing we can do
is to ensure his efforts are not in vain.
If you dare touch Chancellor Shen,
I will go after you, Zhou Hong.
Experiencer's character goal is 60% complete.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I have something to report.
I said there is no court today.
What brings you here?
This is a matter of utmost urgency.
Oh?
I want to report Chancellor Shen Qingyan.
He used the disaster relief as an excuse
to commit corruption.
Almost all the funds allocated for the disaster relief
were privately embezzled by him.
Rumor has it that he appears to be honest and upright,
but actually has a mountain of gold outside the city.
Your Majesty.
I think he shouldn't return to the capital.
He should just be dismissed from office.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Such a treacherous official
should not stay in Donglin.
Your Majesty.
This Chancellor Shen is two-faced.
He truly deserves to die a thousand times.
Exactly.
The Shen family has all passed away.
What right do you have to slander him?
Th-There's evidence.
Take a look if you don't believe me.
Whether Chancellor Shen has a mountain of gold
outside the city or not, I don't know.
But Chancellor Zhou,
you have more than just one gold mine.
Your Majesty, you cannot say such things.
Look closely.
Every single piece of evidence
was collected by Chancellor Shen,
who worked tirelessly to get them.
That's not true.
Your Majesty, this is not true.
It is that old scoundrel Shen Qingyan.
You don't deserve to mention his name.
Men, drag him out and execute him.
Your Majesty.
Please spare my life.
Save me, Your Majesty.
I am innocent, Your Majesty.
Wait.
Spare my life, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Who else wants to try this sword?
That piece of trash actually killed Zhou Hong,
and made his trusted aides the Left and Right Prime Ministers.
It seems
he's going to make a move on me.
Leave us.
Si Xingxuan.
Get out!
What happened?
Get out of here!
Put your sword down first.
Get out.
What do you mean?
Now that Eunuch Sun and Zhou Hong,
who were holding you back, are dead,
are you going to disregard our partnership
and kick me out?
Or is it
because you've grown soft
on the Grand Princess?
Si Xingxuan.
I was wrong about you.